https://ste-anne.org/privacy/

1. Our Site Privacy Policy
Ste. Anne de Detroit (“us”, “we” or “our”) operates and manages [link] (the “Site”), which is an informational and educational tool for our historic parish. Our privacy policy addresses the kind of information we gather from visitors to our site, and how we use it.
2. Acceptance of this Policy
By using the Site, you accept this Policy. Use of the Site includes browsing the Site’s contents or joining our email list. By submitting information, including personally identifiable information, you grant us the right to transmit, monitor, retrieve, store, and use your information in connection with the operation of the Site, as permitted by applicable law and as stated in this Policy.
3. Information Collected at the Site
We do not collect personally identifiable information unless you choose to voluntarily provide it. Personally identifiable information means information that (directly or indirectly) identifies an individual. Examples includes a combination of an individual’s name, physical address, email address, telephone number, or credit card information. The personal information you submit is kept secure, and we share it only within the Archdiocese of Detroit and with third parties who assist us with the Site.
We also collect anonymous information, which is information that does not (directly or indirectly) identify, and cannot reasonably be expected to be used to identify, you individually. This includes data regarding your use of the Site, such as computer-related information (your browser, your Internet Protocol address, the last URL you visited, and the date and time of day of your login). We or a third party who assists with the Site may send a “cookie” or “pixel tag” to your computer, an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using and certain parts of the Site might require software or other applications to be downloaded and installed on your computer. You may decline to provide this information to us and/or refuse to accept cookies in your browser or install or enable such applications, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result, and some services may not be available. We use the information resulting from these actions to enhance the experience of using the Site, to understand how our Site is used, to investigate and verify proper conduct at the Site, and to monitor the security and integrity of the Site.
Our Site automatically collects the Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses of each computer that accesses and interacts with this Site. However, an IP address is not personally identifiable information and we may use this information as we use other anonymous information on an aggregated basis.
4. Retention of Information
We will retain your information long enough to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, and resolve disputes. Except when required by law or an authorized law enforcement investigation, we will not share any personally identifiable information we receive from you with any parties outside of the Archdiocese of Detroit, with the exception of entities that help us operate the Site
5. Information Sharing
Occasionally, we need to share your personally identifiable information or other sensitive information with certain third parties in order to execute transactions or provide you with services related to the Site. In each case, the reputable third party that receives your personally identifiable or otherwise sensitive information will agree not to use or disclose such information except to help us provide the services offered at, or related to, the Site before receiving, using or creating personally identifiable information.
We may also share anonymous or aggregated data with third parties in connection with the operation of this Site so long as such data does not contain identifying, sensitive or regulated information about any individual unless we receive permission to do so.
6. Opt-in Communications
The Site allows you to opt-in to email or other forms of communications that you can unsubscribe from at any time. To stop receiving communications, you may use the opt-out or unsubscribe functionality within the method of communication or email [email address].
7. Third Party Sites; Applications; Services
In order to provide website users with other helpful information, our Site contains links to other websites and allows you to access other information and materials provided by third parties (examples include Facebook and an article). We do not own or control such other websites and are not responsible for the information provided at those websites. The third parties help us deliver the services offered at the Site and in other ways that help us conduct our business, including hosting of the Site, hosting of data (including personally identifiable information), authorization and processing of payments. We are also not responsible for, and do not control, the functionality or content of such third party applications, including how those applications interact with the technology you use to access the Site. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies of these third parties or how they collect information.
8. Safeguarding your Private Information
Be aware that no method of sending information over the Internet, or any method of electronic storage, is completely secure so we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your information. You are solely responsible for the privacy and security of any information that you share with us. Additionally, if you submit information to us that relates to another person, you represent that you have the authority to do so and permit us to use the information as specified in this Policy.
9. Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that their child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, they should contact us.
10. Updates to the Policy
We may amend this Policy at any time without advanced notice or consent except as required by applicable law. If we make any significant changes to this Policy we will notify you by email, post a notice of such changes on the Site, or flag our Privacy Policy on the Site as updated. You agree to our use of electronic communications with you for purposes of this Policy. If you do not agree to the changes to this Policy, we will continue to maintain and use your personally identifiable information previously collected in accordance with the Policy in force as of that date.
11. Site Contact Information
Please contact us with any questions or comments at:
1000 Ste. Anne Street, Detroit MI 48226
313-496-1701
This Policy was last updated on, and is effective as of November 16, 2017.
The Basilica of Ste. Anne de Detroit was founded in 1701 and is the second oldest continuously operating parish in America. Our beautiful neo-Gothic basilica is an architectural gem in the heart of Detroit. Come and visit our vibrant, diverse parish. All are welcome!
Helpful Links
Basilica Announcement
A New Basilica Video
Bulletin
Father Gabriel Richard
Events
Events
Novena
City
Please select a State...AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
Email*
Follow Us
1000 Sainte Anne Street
Detroit,
MI,
48216
313.496.1701
